JOE：Hello, sit anywhere you like.
JOE：你好，隨便坐啊。
Young Man：Do you have saké?
少年：有清酒嗎？
JOE：Yep, wait one sec.
JOE：有啊，稍等。
JOE：Do you want it heated?
JOE：要加熱嗎？
Young Man：No.
少年：不用了。
JOE：Never seen you before. Are you from the east? Node 03?
JOE：沒見過你耶，東方人？Node 03 來的？
Young Man：Yes. Is it rare to see one around these places?
少年：嗯，這邊很少見嗎？
JOE：Nah, where do you think this is? It's 08, any type of people can be found here.
JOE：怎麼可能，這邊是 08 耶，什麼人都有。
JOE：But cold saké... indeed not an order you see every day.
JOE：點冰清酒的人就真的很少了。
Young Man：Back home we call this "Yukihie", refreshes the brain quite well... *Gulp!*
少年：這在我們那叫「雪冷」，很醒腦……*咕！*
JOE："Yukihie", I see...
JOE：「雪冷」啊……
Young Man：*Gulp!*
少年：*咕！*
JOE：Jasus, slow down. If you get drunk so fast, I'm gonna be the one carrying your limp body outside.
JOE：喂，喝慢點吧，你要是一下就醉了我要負責趕你出去耶。
JOE：I've always had a fond interest in chatting with customers from other Nodes.
JOE：我一直很喜歡跟其他 Node 的客人聊天的。
Young Man：I'm... not exactly the type who's good at chatting.
少年：我……不是很會聊天的那種人。
JOE：Haha, it's fine.
JOE：哈哈，沒關係。
JOE：I'm JOE, and you are?
JOE：我叫 JOE，你呢？
Young Man：Hayato... *Gulp!*
少年：Hayato……*咕！*
JOE：Did you get dumped?
JOE：你是失戀了嗎？
Hayato：……... Why did you ask?
Hayato：……為什麼這麼問？
JOE：Well, a young fella with a depressed look visiting an unfamiliar bar with the sole purpose of getting trashed.
JOE：半夜一個人跑到沒去過的酒吧狂灌酒、一臉憂鬱的年輕人
JOE：Pretty sure that means it has something to do with relationship issues... I think?
JOE：八成是遇到什麼感情上的問題……吧？
Hayato：I'm... looking for a female.
Hayato：我在……找一個女的。
JOE：Girlfriend?
JOE：女朋友？
Hayato：More or less my childhood friend, been missing for years already... *Gulp!*
Hayato：算青梅竹馬吧，已經失蹤好幾年了……*咕！*
JOE：For years... could it be that she already... ah, I'm sorry.
JOE：好幾年……會不會已經……啊，抱歉。
Hayato：No need to be...I gave up a long time ago too.
Hayato：不……其實我也很早之前就放棄了
Hayato：In Node 03, missing people usually stay missing forever. It's practically a part of everyday life.
Hayato：我們都住在 Node 03，人口失蹤找不回來是很平常的事情。
Hayato：However, for some unknown reason, I just always have this feeling that she is right here in Node 08. A very powerful feeling too...*Gulp!*
Hayato：但是我不知道為什麼一直有她就在 Node 08 的感覺，而且很強烈……*咕！*
JOE：... If you're looking for someone, maybe you've come to the right location.
JOE：……要找人的話，也許你來對地方了。
JOE：Not to brag about it, but this little shop really has all kinds of people visiting every day.
JOE：不是我要自誇，這間店真的各式各樣的人都有
JOE：Give me some hints, maybe I can help. If you have a photo, even better.
JOE：你給一些線索，也許我能幫上忙，如果有照片就更好了。
Hayato：A photo... I always have it with me. Here.
Hayato：照片……我隨身都帶著，這裡。
JOE：Hoho, lemme take a look. Heard from folks that Node 03 is where all the cute gals are at...
JOE：喔喔，我看看，聽說 Node 03 專出正妹呢……
JOE：……！
JOE：……！
JOE：...... This person......
JOE：……這個人……